"lang" 
{ 
"Language" "English" 
"Tokens" 
{
"GameUI_GameMenu_Tutorial"		"TUTORIAL"
"GameUI_GameMenu_FiringRange"	"FIRING RANGE"

"Playerid_sameteam"		"Friend: %s1 Health: %s2"
"Playerid_diffteam"		"Enemy: %s1"
"Playerid_noteam"		"%s1 Health:%s2"
"Team"				"Team %s1"

"Tutorial_TAC_Reset"		"Trial reset."
"Tutorial_TAC_Finish"		"All targets destroyed!"
"Tutorial_TAC_Blocked"		"You must destroy all targets\nbefore you proceed"
"Tutorial_Range_Hint"		"You can change your weapon\nand class at any time\nby opening the class menu."
"Tutorial_Pit_Wallrun"		"WALL RUNNING: You can gain speed by moving diagonally\ninto flat vertical surfaces whilst looking forward."
"Tutorial_Pit_Bhop"			"BUNNY HOPPING: Maintain speed by chaining\nconsecutive jumps one after another. Strafing\ncan give greater control over direction."
"Tutorial_Pit_Wiggle"		"WIGGLE RUNNING: Additional speed can be gained by quickly\nstrafing left and right whilst moving forward."
"Tutorial_Pit_Ramp"			"RAMP BOOST: A large speed boost can be earned by jumping\noff of certain ramps the instant you land on them."
"Tutorial_Pit_Wallrun_Low"	"Resistance set to: Low"
"Tutorial_Pit_Wallrun_Med"	"Resistance set to: Medium"
"Tutorial_Pit_Wallrun_Hig"	"Resistance set to: High"
"Tutorial_Pit_Wallrun_Na"	"Resistance set to: None"

"Tutorial_Hint_1"			"Welcome to the JH INDUSTRIES mental and\nphysical readiness training program.\nThis program will test your abilities\nand demonstrate tactics for field operations."
"Tutorial_Hint_2"			"Please proceed forwards."
"Tutorial_Hint_3_Recon"		"Retrieving user information... Type: Recon\nPreparing configuration."
"Tutorial_Hint_3_Assault"	"Retrieving user information... Type: Assault\nPreparing configuration."
"Tutorial_Hint_3_Support"	"Retrieving user information... Type: Support\nPreparing configuration."
"Tutorial_Hint_4_Recon"		"Reconnaissance units, or simply Recons, excel\nin fast movement, and can take advantage\nof areas other classes cannot enter due to their slim\nstature and long-jump capabilities."
"Tutorial_Hint_4_Assault"	"Assault units are a jack of all trades. They\nhave limited sprint power and thermoptic\ncamouflage, but come armed with some powerful\nequipment- including a HE fragmentation grenade."
"Tutorial_Hint_4_Support"	"The Support unit carries heavier armour than\nany other. This enhanced protection comes\nat the cost of movement speed and no thermoptic\ncamouflage, but good use of their smoke grenades\ncan turn the tides of any battle."
"Tutorial_Hint_5_Recon"		"To long jump, jump whilst sprinting."
"Tutorial_Hint_5_Assault"	"Try to complete these simple jumps. Crouching\nwhilst jumping can help you reach higher areas."
"Tutorial_Hint_5_Support"	"As a support, your size and limited jumping ability\nprevents you from entering some areas, like\nvents or high ledges. It is important to be aware of\nthreats that may lie in unreachable areas."
"Tutorial_Hint_6_Recon"		"Recons are equipped with night vision lenses. Using night vision\nin dim areas can raise awareness of potential threats."
"Tutorial_Hint_6_Assault"	"Assaults have access to motion vision, which will highlight any\nmoving person or object, including those utilising\nthermoptic camouflage.\n \nThe effect will be demonstrated by this hachikoma."
"Tutorial_Hint_7"			"Smoke will obscure your vision, and can blind\nyou entirely for as long as you are within the cloud."
"Tutorial_Hint_8"			"However, support units can use their thermal vision to see\nclearly through smoke, so it is wise to be cautious around smoke\nif you are unable to see through the smoke yourself."
"Tutorial_Hint_8_Xtra"		"Additionally, thermal vision can be used to spot most\nthreats, and is useful in large areas where targets may not be\neasily distinguished.\nNote that thermal vision is ineffective against combatants\nusing thermoptic camouflage."

"Tutorial_Weps_1"			"Your secondary weapon can often save your life in\nthe field- if you run out of ammo or have no time\nto reload your primary weapon, swiftly reaching\nfor your secondary is a good plan B."
"Tutorial_Weps_2_R"			"As a Recon, your secondary weapon is the Milso (KGH-5).\nThe Milso has lackluster stopping power but is suppressed, which\ncan help you remain hidden when cloaked if you\ndon't already have a supressed weapon at hand."
"Tutorial_Weps_2_A"			"As an Assault, your secondary weapon is JH INDUSTRIES' Tachi.\nThe Tachi can switch between semi-automatic and full auto\nfire modes, which can allow you to quickly finish off\na target at medium to close range."
"Tutorial_Weps_2_S"			"As a Support, your secondary weapon is the Sanjuro Kyla-9.\nThe Kyla has a considerable amount of stopping\npower, even at distance when handled correctly.\nKeep a strong grip when firing, as the recoil can hinder\nconsecutive shots."
"Tutorial_Weps_3"			"Try your secondary weapon on these actors. You can\nreplenish your ammo by using the interactable node."
"Tutorial_Weps_4_R"			"Recons can make use of the remote detonation pack, which\nas the name implies, is an explosive that\ncan be detonated from anywhere.\nYou are only granted access to an RDP at Corporal rank."
"Tutorial_Weps_4_A"			"Assaults have access to a single fragmentation grenade, which\nis ideal for dealing lethal damage to targets behind corners, or\nwho are otherwise not within line of fire."
"Tutorial_Weps_4_S"			"Support units typically carry two smoke grenades\non their person. As previously mentioned, smoke\ncan effectively shut down areas from those who\ncannot see through it."
"Tutorial_Weps_5_R"			"Destroy these targets with the explosive. The blast radius\nis large, so stand clear before you turn the switch."
"Tutorial_Weps_5_A"			"Destroy the targets with grenades."
"Tutorial_Weps_6"			"Most firearms can penetrate thin surfaces and\nglass, with the exception of shotguns.\nWith the Murata SUPA-7, you can load slug\nrounds which allow you to penetrate these\nsurfaces."
"Tutorial_Weps_7"			"Eliminate the actor behind the glass using slug rounds.\nEach shot must be loaded individually."
"Tutorial_Weps_8"			"This object is called a 'ghost'. It holds sensitive\ninformation and it will often be your primary\nobjective to retrieve it."
"Tutorial_Weps_9"			"While holding and connected to a ghost, you\ncan effortlessly breach hostile coordination\nsystems via satellite uplink. With this you will\nbe able to see hostile units through walls."
"Tutorial_Weps_10"			"It is advised that you relay this information\nto other members of your squad, as you\nare left almost defenseless whilst connected\nto a ghost."
"Tutorial_Bugout"			"ERROR_UNRECOGNISED_CONNec8t09O9o847tvwaA9#IB^W4,*Mw(vIT#U;IoOUO4E2IdyFEv8j2lTNL7vh;Y-gAoohckfg0U-ZAs(e^;ABIzAq1d32a2q,nE1He6&Wm_8_i"

"Tutorial_Bind_Menu"		".OPEN CLASS MENU VIA %classmenu%"
"Tutorial_Bind_Use"			".INTERACT WITH %+use%"
"Tutorial_Bind_Sprint"		".SPRINT WITH %+sprint%"
"Tutorial_Bind_Vision"		".TOGGLE VISION MODE WITH %+vision%"
"Tutorial_Bind_Mode"		".SWITCH WEAPON MODE VIA %+attack2%"
"Tutorial_Bind_Slug"		".LOAD SLUG AFTER FIRING WITH %+attack2%"
"Tutorial_Bind_Drop"		".DROP WEAPON WITH %+toss%"

"Game_connected"			"%s1 connected"
"Game_disconnected"			"%s1 has left the game"
} 
}
